Yeah. Uh, proud, not surprised by the
response our guys had. You know, we
expected to come down here and, you
know, a lot of questions about how these
guys are going to respond. Uh, we saw
how they would respond all week. We knew
how they'd respond. And to come down
here and put together the poor
performance they did, especially
settling down at halftime and coming out
and getting four straight turnovers,
three three turnovers, the turnover
rundowns. Offense responded with four
straight touchdowns. Special teams units
doing a great job controlling the field
position the entire second half. Uh,
just just really proud. Again, not
surprised by the response we had.
>> Felt like the game kind of got in your
favor with that off schedule.
What did you see from that?
>> That's usually how it works. I mean,
they had a tough time containing Drew
today. Um, but Drew is just Mr.
Reliable. You know, he's in there in
protection. Has a great feel, very
similar to the Buffalo touchdown he
scored a couple years ago. Same
protection where he's just got this
awareness where Joe needs my help right
now. I'm out of the protection world and
and I got to go find a way. And and he
was trying to score, man. I was trying
to hope he stayed in bounds to keep the
clock running there at the end of the
half, but Drew was he was helping on
getting in the end zone. And so again,
that's a huge play right there by by Joe
and by Drew and by the protection to
give him the time to be able to extend
the play like that.
>> Yeah, they're explosive team. Uh they're
really tough to defend, especially in
the run game with the play actions off
of it. They did a nice job in the first
half finding a rhythm, but I thought our
defense really did a great job settling
down and knocking those down for two or
three yards and putting them in passing
situations. You know, with a rookie
quarterback, we knew that was going to
be challenging. And so, I thought the
defense had a great response. You know,
the big touchdown run. Yeah, they got us
on it. They've gotten a lot of people on
that, but I thought the response after
that was really good by the D.
>> You guys started, you know, utilizing
all your weapons. You know, it's T here
and then Jamar and Chase Brown. Is this
kind of an example of how your offense
can
play to perfection.
>> Yeah, I I you know, I feel like we've
shown this a million times over the
years, you know, and unfortunately this
year we just haven't haven't been able
to do it. But this is no surprise. I
mean, I was walking off field Drew
Sample and he said, "This is how I'm
used to these games going, you know,
when we're when we got everybody on
offense ready to roll." And um so again,
we we've got another opportunity this
week against Arizona to come back home
and do it in front of our fans and and I
expect our guys to respond the right
way.
>> I know you're in the game. Is it
bittersweet?
this is what you wanted it to feel like
going into a
>> conference. It it is what it is. You
know, this is the this is the situation
we're in and this is what we can
control. And so, um, after the season,
you'll have a chance to reflect back on
on things that we got to do differently.
But I think right now, this is all we
could control this week was what was our
response in the building, um, to to, you
know, a lot of people after us right
now. And so, the response was tremendous
by our guys. And to put together such a
complete game, I thought was really
impressive.
>> Speaking of seen it a million times,
those two jump balls. How big was it to
kind of get him double coming back up?
>> Yeah, I mean it was I told Jamar to come
punch me in the stomach. We hadn't
thrown double go by the midway point in
the second quarter. So, we got to it a
little earlier than I had initially
planned. We were backed up. It felt like
the moment to go do it. And T did what T
does. He goes up and gets it. Then we
ran the double move there on the goal
line. I thought he did a great job with
his patience, so Joe had time to get it
up and T, you know, he's caught so many
touchdowns in that back right corner of
the end zone getting getting his two
feet in. So, um, expected nothing less
from that connection. expectations for
Chase Brown and I know you still have
two games to go, but we look at what
he's been able to do for you guys on
offens.
>> Yeah, it was great. I I think Chase um
is a is a huge weapon for us and does a
great job with his explosiveness.
Tremendous matchup in the past game as
well that he probably doesn't get enough
credit for. He's won a lot of those
choice routes underneath and um he
caught a CO for a touchdown today when
he was matched up on a backer and so
again he's been a great weapon for us.
I'm happy I have him. I'm I'm good with
the direction he's heading.
>> Seemed like he started with DJ. He tried
to go. Yeah, you got you got JB and
Newton come up come up.
>> Yeah, I mean DJ was battling the flu,
you know, so for him to even get out
there and get IVs and go out there and
play it'd be hard to get through an
entire game. So, uh, certainly
appreciate DJ doing what he did and
fighting through it. And then
fortunately, we got to a point where we
were able to get him out. And, you know,
if anybody's got the flu, you get midway
point in the game, it's going to beat
you up pretty good. Um, so again, I
appreciate DJ doing everything he could
to to get to this game and get through
it.
>> Yeah. Awesome. And I I saw DJ Ivy at the
end of the, you know, making good
contested play towards the end. So, I
thought the response was great. I
thought JD's pick was was awesome. Um,
and all those turnovers those guys got
was a lot of them were combination plays
where one guy was knocking it out, one
guy was tipping it, the other guy's
making the play. Uh, JD's was just
one-on-one man coverage, went up, made a
play. It was big time.
>> What's the feeling like
you guys
>> that we have to finish? That we exactly
what I thought was we have to finish,
you know, and um I've got a lot of
respect for the Dolphins and the
coaching staff there. They're really
good coaches, good people. Um, but we
needed to have a killer instinct to
finish that game out, you know, and so
we wanted to continue to be aggressive
till about the midway point in that
fourth quarter. But, uh, for our guys,
for our sake, for our identity moving
forward, you know, we need to have a
killer instinct and keep throwing the
football and keep finding ways to finish
drives and not let them try to get any
hope and creep back in the game. And I
thought our guys did a great job of
that.
>> Okay, thank you.